coupontweet.com 2012-05-24

# CouponTweet.com

Coupon Tweet is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our many offerings. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. This Privacy Statement only covers the site Coupon Tweet. 

##  P3P 

Coupon Tweet is in compliance with the current draft of the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) Platform for Privacy Preferences (P3P) specification, http://www.w3c.org/P3P, dated April 16, 2002. This specification was developed to allow users to more easily evaluate the use of personal information collected by the web sites they visit. Thus, if your browser is Microsoft Internet Explorer Version 6, or later, your browser can electronically interpret the P3P version of our privacy policies. 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

##  Collection and use of Personal Information 

Providing personal information is voluntary. Coupon Tweet will collect and use personal information about you to respond to your request for products and services offered through this website. We will also collect information in order to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. Once you register with Coupon Tweet and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. The information we collect may be from the following sources: 

  * Information provided by you in connection with obtaining financial products or services such as mortgage loans (such as full name, telephone number, and self-assessed property value). 
  * Information you provide us when you register for a user account to receive communications from us (such as your email address). 
  * Information you provide us when you enter promotions or sweepstakes offered by Coupon Tweet or our co-branded/partnership sites (such as your full name, physical address and email address). 
  * Information you provide us through surveys, feedback, or other forms hosted on our website or the pages of a Coupon Tweet partner/affiliates. 

We also collect demographic information. Demographic information is all other information such as gender, zip code, or any information that is not tied to your personal information. In addition, we might receive information about you from other sources (such as service providers) for tracking purposes. We may add the information we receive about you to your existing account. Like other websites, we also automatically receive and record certain types of information every time you visit us. We use "cookies" and the other information to enhance your experience and present you with personalized offers. See "Cookies and IP Addresses" section below. 

##  With whom your Information may be shared 

Coupon Tweet does not sell trade or rent your personal information to other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

Service Requests or Loan Products - If you submit a request for a loan product or service offered through this website we will share the personal information contained in your request form, such as your full name, physical address, telephone number, property location and self-assessed value, with lenders in our provider network strictly to process and fulfill your request. All lenders in our provider network, which include banks, mortgage lenders and brokers, have entered into marketing agreements with Coupon Tweet and are required to comply with federal and state privacy regulations. The lenders may contact you by telephone, email, or mail based on the information you provided to us in order to process and fulfill your request, even if you have opted into the National Do Not Call List administered by the Federal Trade Commission or any state equivalent Do Not Call List. If one of the lenders contacts you by telephone and you wish not to be contacted again by that lender with respect to your inquiry, then you should specifically make a request to that lender not to contact you again. If the lender disregards your request and contacts you again, please let us know immediately by sending an email to Coupon Tweet Customer Support. Please note that the lenders may maintain the information you provided whether you elect to use their services or not. 

Other Service or Products Requests - If you submit a request for a product or service other than a loan such telecommunication service, we will share the personal information contained in your request form such as your full name, telephone number and email address with our business partners to process and fulfill your request. Our business partners may contact you by telephone, email, or mail based on the information you provided to us, even if you have opted into the National Do Not Call List administered by the Federal Trade Commission or any state equivalent Do Not Call List. If one of our partners contacts you by telephone and you wish not to be contacted again by that business partner with respect to your inquiry, then you should specifically make a request to that partner not to contact you again. 

Vendors - We sometimes disclose the information we collect to companies that host certain services for us such as marketing distribution services on our behalf. These vendors only have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, and may not share it with others or use it for any other purpose. These companies are subject to confidentiality agreements with us and other legal restrictions that prohibit them from using the information except to market the specified Coupon Tweet products or services. 

As Permitted by Law - We may be required to share your personal information with law enforcement or government agencies in response to subpoenas, court orders, federal/state audits or similar circumstances. We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Coupon Tweet's Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law. 

Business Transfer - As with any other business, it is possible that Coupon Tweet in the future could merge with or be acquired by another company. If such an acquisition occurs, the successor company would have access to the information maintained by Coupon Tweet, including customer account information, but would continue to be bound by this privacy policy unless you consent otherwise. We will provide notice in this instance as defined in our "Changes to this Privacy Policy" section below. 

##  Cookies and IP Addresses 

To serve you faster and with better quality, we use "cookies" technology. Cookies are small bits of code, usually stored on a user's computer hard drive, which enable a Web site to "personalize" itself for each user. We generally use cookies to reduce the time it takes for pages to load on your computer and to assist with customer tracking. Customer tracking (or "click-stream") data collected by us is used to optimize your experience by learning whether or not you successfully used Coupon Tweet. Cookies are not tied to your personal information. Additionally, we may capture click-stream data on some of our partner's web sites, limited to the activity involved with the completion of offers listed on our web site. This information is used to monitor the performance of our partners. We also allow select third-parties to set cookies on our website. For example, we use a tracking service, Revenue Science, that uses cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about our visitors. This aggregate visitor usage information collected on Coupon Tweet and used by the Revenue Science network for the purposes of delivering relevant advertising to our audience. Other examples include session cookies when accessing the Blog section of the website. These cookies simply track the session and are not tied to your personal information. We also keep track of Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. An IP Address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer every time you log on to the Internet. 

##  Clear Gifs 

We employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs) that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movement of Web users. Clear gifs are not tied to users' personally identifiable information. We also use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails the recipients have opened. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. If users would like to opt-out of these emails, please see the Opt-out section within any email you receive from us or unsubscribe from our homepage. 

##  Confidentiality and Security 

The security of your personal information is very important at Coupon Tweet and we take a number of steps to safeguard it. For example: We limit access to personal information to those employees or agents who assist us in providing requested products and services to you. Employees are required to comply with our strict policies and procedures regarding the handling of your personal information. Employees who violate these policies are subject to our normal disciplinary process. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard personal information about you. We use industry standard data encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data on the Coupon Tweet website. 

##  Opting-Out 

You may register to receive communications from us directly on our website or through a third party. When you subscribe, we will periodically send you a newsletter e-mail featuring special and exclusive offers, promotions and other members-only benefits. If you no longer wish to receive these communications, please let us know by contacting Customer Care, or click the unsubscribe link located at the bottom of all emails, or use the unsubscribe link located in the footer of our site, Coupon Tweet. Our email database is updated continually. However, you may continue to receive email communications from us up to ten business days from the time we receive your unsubscribe request. Please note that Coupon Tweet can only control its own mailing list and policies. Third party advertisers that maintain their own mailing lists may send communications that advertise our services, and you may need to contact these parties directly in order to stop receiving their email communications. 

##  Message Boards/Chat Rooms/Blogs 

If you use a message board, chat room, or blog on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. 

##  Third Party Links 

This Privacy Policy applies to all information that you provide to Coupon Tweet. However, when you visit websites to which Coupon Tweet provides a link, keep in mind you will be interacting with a third party that operates under its own privacy and security policy. If you choose to obtain certain services through a third party site, the data collected by the third party is governed by that third party's privacy policy. A third party site will also have its own policy regarding the use of cookies and clear gifs. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any other service provider from whom you request services. 

If Coupon Tweet receives personal information from a third party that is not in conjunction with a service offered on our site, the use and disclosure of such information is governed by the agreement (if any) between Coupon Tweet and such third party. 

##  Framing 

In some cases, we may use third party vendors to operate portions of the Coupon Tweet website. Although the particular section of the website may have a similar appearance as the Coupon Tweet site, information submitted through these outside third parties are subject to this Privacy Policy unless otherwise stated. For example, personal information submitted through our Affiliate Program is subject to our Affiliate Program operator's privacy policy. 

##  Children 

We are committed to protecting the privacy of children. Coupon Tweet's services are not written, intended, or designed for children under the age of 13. We do not collect personal information from any person we actually know is under the age of 13\. 

##  Updating your Information 

If you want to access or update the personal information you submitted to Coupon Tweet, please contact Coupon Tweet Customer Support. In the alternative, you can write us at the address below and request that your personal information be updated. 

##  Questions and Suggestions 

If you have any questions, concerns or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, you may contact us by sending us a message via email using the Customer Care form, or by sending a letter to: 

Coupon Tweet   
Attn: Customer Support   
224 W. Huron Street, Suite 6E   
Chicago, IL 60654 

##  Retention of Information 

Any information we collect may be retained for an indeterminate period of time. Certain detail, particularly sensitive data such as financial information, is only maintained until it is successfully transferred to the partner doing the service fulfillment. 

##  Who is collecting your Information 

Unless otherwise noted, your information is being collected solely by Coupon Tweet. See the Section titled "With whom your information may be shared" above concerning the circumstances under which certain of your information may be disclosed to third parties. 

##  Changes to this Privacy Policy 

All versions of this privacy policy are dated with the effective date (the date on which the policy was posted to Coupon Tweet) Coupon Tweet will only use the information we learn about you in the manner described in the Privacy Policy in effect when the information was collected from you. However, we reserve the right to change the terms of this Privacy Policy at any time by posting revisions to our site. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

##  Effect of Privacy Policy 

This privacy policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or legal rights in or on behalf of any party. As noted above, we may revise this privacy policy from time to time in our sole discretion. 

Effective Date January 20, 2009   
Last Updated on January 20, 2009
